Guide to the Music Department records, 1898-2004 RG0075
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office of Choral Activities, 1898-2001; RG0075 Series 4; 9.5 Linear feet (Box 9, Box 8, Box 7, Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 13, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 6)
  - Forms, Correspondence, Lists re trip to California - Troubadours, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 105
  - 49 Copies of letterhead marked "Troubadours on Tour" re trip to California - Troubadours, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 106
  - Mostly Correspondence re trip to California - Troubadours, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 107
  - Mostly Correspondence re trip To California - Troubadours, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 108
  - Maps, Programs re trip to California, Plaque for Alumni Hosts in California- Troubadours, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 109
  - Brochures, Instructions, Correspondence Re trip to California - Troubadours, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 110
  - Mostly Photos - Alumni Chorus, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 111
  - Photo Album - Harmon Choral Associates or Alumni Chorus, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 112: empty folder
  - Photos, Lists - Alumni Chorus, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 113
  - Correspondence, Lists, Photos of Harmon Choral Associates Board - Alumni Singers, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 114
  - Photos, GW Times, checkbook - Troubadours and 1986 Reunion, 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 115
  - Photo Album (Bob Hope photo in one) - Troubadours, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 116: empty folder
  - 6 Envelopes of negatives and 82 photos - Troubadours, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 117
  - Mostly General Correspondence - Troubadours, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 118
  - Financial Records - Troubadours, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 119
  - Correspondence, phone tree - Troubadours, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 120
  - 8 envelopes of photos, some with many photos on sheets in envelopes Troubadours, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 121
  - Correspondence re Performances, Critique of Tape by Troubadours, Rehearsal Schedules, "Thank You" notes, Instructions, Posters - Troubadours, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 122
  - Posters, Programs, newsletter, informal notes, correspondence, contact sheets- 1990 Choral Alumni Reunion, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 123
  - Troubadours/Glee Club/University Singers Reunion - posters, programs, informal notes, correspondence, photos, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 123a
  - Letter, photos, sheet music - 1990 Choral Alumni Reunion April (Box 9, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 124
  - GW Choral Activity, negatives, photos, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 124a
  - Alumni Reunion, program, Trip to France, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    formerly folder 124b
  - Flier, Photos, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    formerly folder 124c
  - Photos of Troubadours, negative, contact sheet, 1990 ca. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    formerly folder 124d
  - Minutes of Troubadours Meeting of 3/7/90 - Troubadours, 03/07/1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 125; empty folder
  - Medal, Brochures, Advertisement Folder, Program re trip to Paris, Spring of 1990 - Troubadours Spring (Box 10, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 125a
  - Brochures, Contact Sheet of Photos, Correspondence, Programs re Trips to Paris, spring 1990 - Troubadoursspring (Box 10, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 125b
  - Photo, correspondence, programs, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 125c
  - Correspondence, Newsletter re trips to Italy and California, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 126
  - Correspondence, itinerary, budget re trip to Paris - Troubadours Spring, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 127
  - Correspondence re trip to Paris- Troubadours spring, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 128
  - Signed note from Barbara Bush, General Memorabilia of Rehearsals, HCA Award, Concert, Letter - Troubadour, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 129
  - Sheet Music - No dates but obviously for Troubadours - Troubadours, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 130
  - Programs of Concerts for Troubadours, Instructions re trip to California, photos,Calendar for Troubadours, Programs for University Singers - Troubadours, University Singers, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 131
  - Photographs of Rehearsals, Reunions of Troubadours, Parties, Harmon Award Ceremony and Programs for Concerts - Troubadours, University Singers, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 132
  - Photographs, programs, letter to University Singers - Troubadours, University Singers, Alumni, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 133
  - Posters re Troubadours trip to Italy. Sheet Music, programs, photos, financial correspondence & records, lodging records & photos, general correspondence - Troubadours, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 134
  - Programs, trip to Italy by Troubadours, art books, numerous letters on all phases of trip, newspaper clippings, banner/insignia, plus videotape of Troubadours on Italian TV - Troubadours, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    formerly folder 135
  - Sarah Anderson's Newspaper, Program at National Cathedral, Material and Programs of Troubadours' New England Trip, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    formerly folder 136
  - Glee Club Reunion, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    formerly folder 137
  - Troubadours photos, contact sheets, 1990 ca. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    formerly folder 138
  - Article on "Doc" Harmon and his years at GW by David M. Bates, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    formerly folder 139
  - Misc. Glee Club Material, 1900 ca.-1930 -- --ca. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    formerly folder 140
  - Slides of Troubadours, 1960 ca. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    formerly folder 141
  - Medal awarded to the Troubadours by the French-American Society of Orleans, France, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Medal given to the Troubadours by Ambassador Curley, US Ambassador to France, following their performance at his residence in Paris, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Plaque - In Appreciation for Courtesies and Generous Hospitality During the California Tour of 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Framed group photo of Troubadours, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Plaque - Presented to Dr. Robert Harmon, United States Air Force Singing Contest, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Plaque - To Robert Howe Harmon In Grateful Appreciation of His Untiring Efforts in Behalf of The George Washington University Glee Clubs, 05/12/1936 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Reel-to-reel audio recording of Handel's Messiah, 1940 ca. -1960 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Videocassette - Glee Club and Troubadour Alumni Reunion, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Videocassette - GWU Troubadours on Italian television show "Una Matina", undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Departmental files, 1943-1994; RG0075 Series 5; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains programs, newspaper clippings, and photographs. These materials date from 1943-94.
  The subject is troubadours and choral music.
  - Programs and announcements for GWU music events, 1943-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence re: Troubadours' performances and director, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper articles, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photos of performances (including program for "Semele"), undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Thesis: An analysis of the tonal systems of a representative group of English ballad operas of 1728-1738 by Rosemary Nothdurft Killam, 1968; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Thesis: An analysis of symphonic programming techniques of the leading orchestras at the turn of the 20th century, drawn from selected programs of the Boston and Chicago Symphony Orchestras, 1881-1908 by William Paul Toutant, 1972; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Thesis: Analysis and evaluation of the representative groups of works in the brass ensemble literature, grades II-VI, selected from the Virginia Band and Orchestra directors' association manual, as applied to the Alexandria, Virginia, public schools' instrumental music program by Timothy Allen Lutz, 1979; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Thesis: Ruth Crawford Seeger, preserver of American Folk Music by Karen Mandeville Cardullo, 1980; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Thesis: The composer as social critic, a study of five Menotti Operas by Joyce Bell, 1982; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Thesis: Melodic and harmonic practice in European hymnody and psalmody, 1500-1650 by Gary T. Starr, 1987; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Thesis: Musical instruments: their implications concerning musical life in colonial Annapolis by David Kenneth Hildebrand, 1987; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Thesis: A pathway to the will: coherence in theatrics, music, and idea through the concept of dreaming in the Act I "Transformation Scene" of Wagner's Parsifal by Joseph S. Berney, 1992; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Thesis: "Ung gay bergier" Transcriptions from sixteenth-century lute intabulations with a comparative analysis by Carolyn Anderson Surrick, 1992; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Thesis: The works of Mary Howe: a survey of performance history and critical response by Denise N. Allen, 1992; Series 5 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Department files, 1985-1996; RG0075 Series 6; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains brochures, correspondence, travel documents, minutes, articles, from troubadour trips to Italy and Czech Republic. This material covers the dates 1985-96.
  - Troubadours - Trip to Italy - misc. fliers, brochures, correspondence, newspaper clippings, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Troubadours - Trip to Italy - misc. fliers, brochures, correspondence, travel documents, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Troubadours - Trip to Italy - misc. maps, correspondence, travel documents, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Troubadours - misc. correspondence, newsletters, meeting minutes, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Troubadours - Trip to Czech Republic - misc. fliers, travel documents, correspondence, maps, brochures, newspaper articles, postcards, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Troubadours - misc. correspondence, programs, fliers, club documents, 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Department files, 1959; RG0075 Series 7; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains notes and program from the "Mikado" and photo of choral society performing Handel's "Messiah." The materials date from 1959.
  Previously Accession #687.
- Images, Recordings, and Scrapbook, ca.1930-1996; RG0075 Series 8; 2 Linear Feet (Box 1)
  This series contains photographs, contact sheets, photographic negatives, slides, a scrapbook, a DVD, a VHS tape, CDs, and audio cassettes. Photograph and slide subjects include the Troubadours, honors recitals, Coolidge Quartet, Neil Tilkens, Roy Guenther, Tzvetan Konstantinov, Robert Parris, George Steiner, Marilyn Garst, Sura Kim, Catherine Pickar, Denise Newbold Allen, Petworth School, opera, Anner Bylsma, staff holiday parties, University Singers, audio visual lab, choir, Canadian Brass ensemble, Dr. Gottfried Wagner, PAS Brass, Tito Puento, and Mary McCartry. The scrapbook contains photos from Troubadour trips to Iceland, Greenland, Bermuda, Azores, etc, newspaper clippings, greeting cards, correspondence. Recordings include band concerts, guest lectures, seminars, and student recitals. The materials dates from circa 1920 to 2005.
  - Troubadours - 1920s, 1920-1929 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Troubadours - 1930s, 1930-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Troubadours - 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Troubadours - 1950s, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Troubadours - 1960s, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Troubadours - 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Troubadours - 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Troubadours - Retreat, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Troubadours - Italy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Troubadours - Prague, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Troubadours - Retreat, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Troubadours - random photos, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Troubadours - Misc. correspondence, programs, newspaper articles, newsletters, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Binder - photos from trips to Iceland, Greenland, Bermuda, Azores, etc; newspaper clippings, greeting cards, correspondence, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives, 1984-1998 and undated; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Subjects include honors recitals, Coolidge Quartet, Neil Tilkens, Roy Guenther, Tzvetan Konstantinov, Robert Parris, George Steiner, Marilyn Garst, Sura Kim, Catherine Pickar, Denise Newbold Allen, Petworth School, opera, Anner Bylsma, staff holiday parties, University Singers, audio visual lab, and choir.
  - Photographs and Program -- "Amahl and the Night Visitors" -- Rehearsal Shots, MC Studio, December 1981; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photographs -- Canadian Brass Concert and Workshops, 27 October 1993-28 October 1993; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Photographs -- Dr. Gottfried Wagner, 25 January 1995; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photographs -- Music Department Holiday Party, December 1991; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photographs and Negatives-- PAS Brass, 1996; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Photographs and Negatives -- Tito Puento, October 1991-April 1992; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photographs -- Troubadours in Ireland, Fall 1990; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Photographs and Negatives -- University Singers, December 1985; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographic Negatives, undated; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Slides -- Mary McCartry at Kennedy Center, 30 October 1991; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Slides, December 1991; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Subjects include choral concert and holiday party
  - DVD -- "When ET Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest", 2004; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Dvd 1)
    Written, composed, and co-directed by James Levy. Directed and choreographed by Gesel Mason and Krissie Marty. Produced by Cheles Rhynes. Animations by Chris Ruch. Cast and Musicians: Erich Parker, Ray Bugnosen, Nikki Strong, Patty Reese, Melissa Norwood, Michelle Vignoli, Reggie Cole, C.J. Holm, Liza Predergast, Dede Wyland, Bonnie Harris, Jim Levy, John Albertson, Dan Conway, Francis Thompson, Chris Ntaka, Dave Marsh, Nancy Snider, Carey Creed, Beck Levy, and Alexandra Levy.
  - VHS -- GWU University Seminars, "Theatre in the Community," with Molly Smith and Ida Prosky, 16 November 1998; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Videocassette 1)
  - CD -- Suzzane Post, undated; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cd 1)
    1. "Je dis que rien ne m'epourante," Georges Bizet 2. "Sinore, Ascoita!" Giacomo Puccini
  - CD -- Leslie Vaeth, Capstone 2006, "The Telephone", RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cd 2)
  - CD -- The George Washington University Band -- Sampler 1999-2005, RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cd 3)
    Conductor, Ben Fritz
  - CD -- The George Washington University Department of Music, Jazz Program CD 2002-2003, RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cd 4)
    Recorded live at the GWU Jazz Festival, 11 April 2003.
  - CD -- The George Washington University Bands, "Music for the Millennium", 10 February 2000; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cd 5)
  - CD -- The George Washington University Bands, Colonials Weekend Concert, 23 October 2005; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cd 6)
  - CD -- Honors, Sara, undated; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cd 7)
  - Audio Cassette -- Jonathan Kantor, Tenor Saxophone, undated; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cassette 1)
  - Audio Cassette -- John Corigliano, Guest Lecture, 20 April 1998; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cassette 2)
  - Audio Cassette -- Parabolae Salomonis by Robert Parris, undated; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 2, Cassette 3)
  - Photographic Negatives and Contact Sheets -- Oversize, 1984 and undated; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographic Negatives and Contact Sheets -- Oversize -- University Singers and Harmon Awards, 1991; RG0075 Series 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Vinyl Record - The Traveling Troubadours, 1986; 0.25 Linear Feet Two vinyl records of the 1986 Troubadours, directed by Catherine Pickar. (Box SHARED Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Harmon Choral Associates Records, 1982-2001; RG0075 Series 9; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
    This series contains Harmon Choral Associates records. Included is correspondence, newsletters, membership lists, reunions, meeting minutes, by-laws, and photos. The materials date from 1982-2001 and was donated to University Archives by Cathy Pickar.
    - "Forty Years of Harmony" - History of Dr. Harmon and the GW Glee Club, 1924-1964 by David Bates, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Choral Alumni lists, 1992 ca. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Choral Activities - correspondence, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Choral Activities - correspondence, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Choral Activities - correspondence, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Choral Activities - correspondence, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Choral Activities - correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Glee Club and Troubadour Alumni Reunion Honoring Dr. Harmon - correspondence, list of invitees, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Glee Club and Troubadour Alumni Reunion Honoring Dr. Harmon - correspondence, list of invitees, photos, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Glee Club and Troubadour Alumni Reunion Honoring Dr. Harmon - Registration or acceptance forms, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Glee Club and Troubadour Alumni Reunion Honoring Dr. Harmon - Registration or acceptance forms, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Glee Club and Troubadour Alumni Reunion Honoring Dr. Harmon - Registration or acceptance forms, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Glee Club and Troubadour Alumni Reunion Honoring Dr. Harmon - Registration or acceptance forms, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Choral Activities - correspondence, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, newsletter, alumni list, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, newsletter, photos, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, By-Laws, newsletter, photos, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Harmon Choral Association - Alumni Singers Reunion - correspondence, mailing lists, registration forms, program, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Harmon Choral Association - Alumni Singers Reunion - contact prints and negatives, 04/27/1990 -04/29/1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Harmon Choral Association - Alumni Singers Reunion - photos, 04/28/1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Listing of Choral Singing activities in the student newpspaer "Hatchet,", 1904-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, By-Laws, newsletter, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Harmon Choral Association - photos of booth at Marvin Center for Alumni Weekend, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, minutes, lists of alumni, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, activities, clippings from Hatchet (1953), 1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Harmon Choral Association - Harmon Award photo project winner, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Harmon Choral Association list, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, newsletter, activities, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, By-Laws, activities, cassette of music, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, newsletter, lists, agendas, choral endowment, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, newsletter, list of Board of Advisors, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, newsletter, activities, minutes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, newsletter, minutes, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Harmon Choral Association - correspondence, newsletter, minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Programs and Publicity, 1961-2010; Series 11 (Map-folder 1)
  This series contains programs, newsletters, flyers, clippings, and other publicity material for GW Music Department concerts and recitals, and other departmental events. Materials date between 1961 and 2010.
  - Programs, 1961-1962, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1962-1963, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1963-1964, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1964-1965, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1965-1966, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 1966-1967, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1967-1968, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1968-1969, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Programs, 1969-1970, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Programs, 1970-1971, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Programs, 1971-1972, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Programs, 1972-1973, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Programs, 1973-1974, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Programs, 1974-1975, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Programs, 1975-1976, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Programs, 1976-1977, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Programs, 1977-1978, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Programs, 1978-1979, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Programs, 1979-1980, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Programs, 1980-1981, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Programs, 1981-1982, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Programs, 1982-1983, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Programs, Fall 1983, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Programs, Spring 1984, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Programs, 1984-1985, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Programs, 1985-1986, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Student Recital Programs, 1986-1987, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Programs, 1987-1988, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Programs, 1988-1989, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Programs, 1989-1990, Series 11 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Programs, 1990-1991, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Programs, 1991-1992, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1992-1993, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Programs, Spring 1994, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Programs, Fall 1994, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Programs, Spring 1995, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Programs, Fall 1995, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Programs, Spring 1996, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Programs, Fall 1996, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Programs, Spring 1997, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Programs, Fall 1997, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Programs, Spring 1998, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Programs, Fall 1998, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Programs, Spring 1999, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Programs, Fall 1999, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Programs, 2000, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Programs, 2001, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Programs, 2002, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Programs, 2003, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Programs, 2004, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Programs, 2005, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Programs, 2006, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Programs, 2007, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Programs, 2008, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Programs, 2009, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Programs, 2010, Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Band Programs, 1991-2002, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Band Programs, 1991-2005, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1984-1987, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Programs, 1987-1995, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Programs, 1995-1996, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Programs, 2001-2002, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Recital Flyers 1997-2000, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Concert and Recital Programs, 1997-2004, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - GW Music Newsletter, 1983-1986, Series 11 (Box 3, Folder 9)